

SUHAIB AHMAD

Full-Stack Web Developer

An experienced individual who have what it takes to fulfill a full-stack position. Into coding, but perusing an agenda that includes a minimum of a brief introduction & experience for every part of software development work. Currently, I am working as a full-stack dev based in Jordan and open for a full-time opportunity anywhere worldwide.



SuhaibAhmadAi@hotmail.com





+962-788-424-973





Makkahwi





Makkahwi

Experiences

Senior Full-Stack Dev

Full-Timer

AgileTz | Amman, Jordan

6 Months
Aug 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer

Full-Timer

ArabWork | Amman, Jordan

2 Months Jun - Jul 2022

Frontend Developer

Full-Timer

LuxTag | Cyberjaya, Malaysia

6 Months
May - Oct 2021

Full-Stack Developer

Intern

LuxTag | Cyberjaya, Malaysia

6 Months Nov 2020 - Apr 2021

Full-Stack Developer

Part-Timer

AIS School | KL, Malaysia

12 Months Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

Web Developer

Freelancer
Malaysia & Jordan

7 Years Oct 2015 - Present

Skills



React.Js



Next.Js



Vue.Js



Node.Js



Express.Js



Laravel



Django



Wordpress



PostgreSQL



MySQL



GitHub



Docker



VS Code



JavaScript

Python



jQuery



HTML

JSON



CSS



Bootstrap



Agile



SCRUM



REST API

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science

International Islamic University Malaysia | May 2021

Specialized in Data Science and Computational Intelligence